Speaker 1: You have former New York Governor Andrew Cuomo now running for New York City mayor trying to revive his political career and is entering into that same lane as Gavin now saying Democrats are the reason that our big cities
are falling
Speaker 2: apart. You see a deterioration of conditions and people say
Speaker 3: why and you're all Democrats and I went to Los Angeles and all I saw were blue tarps
Speaker 3: uh everywhere and homeless living under bridges etc and i'm afraid to walk down the street and it's all democrats who are in charge and there's no one else to blame it's you kerry
lake joins us
Speaker 1: now to talk more about it isn't this
Speaker 4: something to see they're obviously changing lanes this is going to be i think where they move to for 28
The
Speaker 5: rats are fleeing the ship. They know the ship
Speaker 6: is sinking. They know they were complicit in it. Look, I've moved beyond Democrat and Republican. We've seen Democrats do terrible things. We've seen some Republicans do terrible things. The question is, are you pro-America? And allowing people to fester on the streets, waste their human potential by encouraging them with policy to remain homeless, remain in drug addiction, remain mentally ill without about getting them help.
Speaker 6: We've seen as they've wasted and pilfered money that was meant and earmarked to help people who are homeless, and it was in these Democrat cities where that happened. And it's very rich for them now to come out when they realize that the collapse of the Democrat party
Speaker 7: could take them down, that all of a sudden they're the common sense ones, I
Speaker 8: don't know. - Cuomo says that far left forces inside of his party
Speaker 8: You know force
Speaker 9 (lower-pitched voice): them to govern like radicals that they're threatened with primaries if they don't govern the way we've seen them govern and just Tank their cities and tank their states to hell and back and and they're scared of those factions And that's why they do what they do. Is that an excuse? So they
Speaker 10: don't have the let me let me use the right word here. I I don't want to say balls because that's inappropriate
Speaker 6: They don't have the spine to stand up to do a group of people that are wrong
and
Speaker 6: That's disqualifying from here to eternity. If you don't have the courage, when it's you versus people who are radicalized, to stand up and say, "No, that's wrong," then you don't have a leg to stand on. And I'm sorry, but Governor Cuomo was the guy behind so many of our grandparents and great-grandparents festering and dying in nursing homes.
Speaker 6: And what did that segment, that segment of the population choose to do? They tried to blame it on our elementary school age children, saying they were the ones that were killing grandma and grandpa because they weren't masked up and they weren't willing to take a vaccine. To me, that's unforgivable. And if you don't have the courage to stand up to radicalized people in your political party, then you should get out of politics. And frankly, you've lost the respect of the American people.
I want
Speaker 13: to ask you, we watched something
Speaker 9 (lower-pitched voice): that I thought was pretty amazing today at the White House with Ramaphosa from South Africa there. We watched our president do what our president never does in this country, which is actually call someone out. We've seen this a couple of times from Trump, but he made it uncomfortable. He made it awkward. He forced an issue that needed to be forced.
Speaker 9 (lower-pitched voice): against a very terrible guy who came in with a big smile and a lot of BS, like politicians always do. What did you think of today? You
know, President
Speaker 14: Trump is not afraid to be bold and strong for this
Speaker 6: country and the American people, but he's proven to be really, I think it was in Saudi Arabia that the crown prince said he's the president of the world. He's standing up for what's right around the world, and he wants to bring peace to the world. He no longer wants to see countries that are just succumb to war
Speaker 6: and chaos and despair. And one of the worst things I've seen that has gotten the least amount of attention by the media is what's happening in South America, where it's literally racism. You're being killed for the color of your skin, pure and simple, and they are verbalizing it exactly the way that I just described it. And for him to allow this man to come into the Oval Office and call him out in front of the press, who in my opinion is guilty for not covering it,
Speaker 6: He was really calling out the press today. We all knew that this leader of this nation was doing terrible things. But who is who is adding to that? The press who refuses to cover it. He forced them to cover it on live television today. It was a brilliant
Speaker 15: strategy and is bringing to light a very important topic that we need to talk about, which is the racially motivated murders. As much as Peter Alexander over
Speaker 9 (lower-pitched voice): at NBC did not want to talk about it and could not wait to change the subject, which told you everything about NBC News, by the way. Carrie Lake, good to see you. Thank you so much.
Speaker 16: NBC, nothing but communism.
Speaker 9 (lower-pitched voice): That's exactly right.